A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Central Files, Series 3 FA378
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Name File, 1
  - Personal or Organizational - R
    - RIE (Box 139)
    - RIL (Box 139)
    - RIPLEY, S. DILLON, HON. (Box 139)
    - RIS (Box 139)
    - RIV (Box 139)
    - RO (Box 139)
    - ROBERTS, A (Box 140)
    - ROBERTS, N (Box 140)
    - ROBINSON (Box 140)
    - ROBINSON, D (Box 140)
    - ROBINSON, J (Box 140)
    - ROBINSON, M (Box 140)
    - ROC (Box 140)
    - ROCKEFELLER (Box 140)
    - ROD (Box 140)
    - ROG (Box 140)
    - ROH (Box 140)
    - ROM (Box 140)
    - RON (Box 141)
    - ROSE (Box 141)
    - ROSEN (Box 141)
    - ROSENBAUM, RICHARD M. HON. (Box 141)
    - ROSF (Box 141)
    - ROST (Box 141)
    - ROTH (Box 141)
    - ROU (Box 141)
    - ROVINE, ARTHUR W. HON. (Box 141)
    - ROUDEBUSH, RICHARD L., HON. (Box 141)
    - ROW (Box 141)
    - RU (Box 141)
    - RUD (Box 141)
    - RUM (Box 141)
    - RUS (Box 142)
    - RUT (Box 142)
    - RY (Box 142)
  - Personal or Organizational - S
    - S (Box 142)
    - SAD (Box 142)
    - SAG (Box 142)
    - SAI (Box 142)
    - SAL (Box 142)
    - SALO (Box 142)
    - SAM (Box 142)
    - SAN (Box 142)
    - SANF (Box 142)
    - SAR (Box 142)
    - SAT (Box 142)
    - SAV (Box 142)
    - SAW (Box 142)
    - SC (Box 143)
    - SCH (Box 143)
    - SCHE (Box 143)
    - SCHI (Box 143)
    - SCHL (Box 143)
    - SCHM (Box 143)
    - SCHN (Box 143)
    - SCHR (Box 143)
    - SCHU (Box 143)
    - SCHW (Box 143)
    - SCHWE (Box 143)
    - SCI (Box 144)
    - SCO (Box 144)
    - SCOTT, L (Box 144)
    - SCR (Box 144)
    - SCU (Box 144)
    - SE (Box 144)
    - SEB (Box 144)
    - SED (Box 144)
    - SEG (Box 144)
    - SEJ (Box 144)
    - SEM (Box 144)
    - SER (Box 144)
    - SET (Box 144)
    - SEW (Box 144)
    - SH (Box 145)
    - SHAN (Box 145)
    - SHAP (Box 145)
    - SHAR (Box 145)
    - SHAW (Box 145)
    - SHE (Box 145)
    - SHEF (Box 145)
    - SHEN (Box 145)
    - SHER (Box 145)
    - SHI (Box 145)
    - SHIM (Box 145)
    - SHL (Box 145)
    - SHOR (Box 145)
    - SHR (Box 145)
    - SHU (Box 145)
    - SI (Box 146)
    - SIF (Box 146)
    - SIL (Box 146)
    - SIM (Box 146)
    - SIMN (Box 146)
    - SIMP (Box 146)
    - SIN (Box 146)
    - SIS (Box 146)
    - SK (Box 146)
    - SL (Box 146)
    - SLB (Box 146)
    - SLO (Box 146)
    - SM (Box 147)
    - SMITH (Box 147)
    - SMITH, D (Box 147)
    - SMITH, G (Box 147)
    - SMITH, J (Box 147)
    - SMITH, L (Box 147)
    - SMITH, M (Box 147)
    - SMITH, R (Box 147)
    - SMITH, S (Box 147)
    - SMITH, W (Box 147)
    - SMITHA (Box 147)
    - SMO (Box 147)
    - SN (Box 147)
    - SNY (Box 147)
    - SO (Box 148)
    - SOL (Box 148)
    - SOM (Box 148)
    - SOR (Box 148)
    - SOU (Box 148)
    - SP (Box 148)
    - SPE (Box 148)
    - SPEL (Box 148)
    - SPI (Box 148)
    - SPO (Box 148)
    - SQ (Box 148)
    - ST - A-I (Box 148)
    - ST - J (Box 148)
    - ST - K-Z (Box 148)
    - STAATS, ELMER B., THE HON., 1975 (Box 149)
    - STAATS, ELMER B., THE HON., 1976 (Box 149)
    - STA (Box 149)
    - STAF (Box 149)
    - STAN (Box 149)
    - STANL (Box 149)
    - STAR (Box 149)
    - STAT (Box 149)
    - STAU (Box 149)
    - STEA (Box 149)
    - STEI (Box 149)
    - STEL (Box 149)
    - STEV (Box 150)
    - STEW (Box 150)
    - STI (Box 150)
    - STO (Box 150)
    - STON (Box 150)
    - STR (Box 150)
    - STRO (Box 150)
    - STU (Box 150)
    - SU (Box 150)
    - SUL (Box 151)
    - SULLIVAN, K (Box 151)
    - SUM (Box 151)
    - SUT (Box 151)
    - SV (Box 151)
    - SWI (Box 151)
    - SX (Box 151)
  - Personal or Organizational - T
    - T (Box 151)
    - TAG (Box 151)
    - TAL (Box 151)
    - TAM (Box 151)
    - TAS (Box 151)
    - TAYLOR (Box 152)
    - TAYLOR, M (Box 152)
    - TE (Box 152)
    - TEM (Box 152)
    - TER (Box 152)
    - TES (Box 152)
    - THE (Box 152)
    - THOMAS (Box 152)
    - THOMASON (Box 152)
    - THOMPSON (Box 152)
    - THOMPSON, G (Box 152)
    - THOMSON (Box 152)
    - THU (Box 152)
    - TI (Box 153)
    - TIM (Box 153)
    - TOA (Box 153)
    - TOL (Box 153)
    - TON (Box 153)
    - TOR (Box 153)
    - TOW (Box 153)
    - TR (Box 153)
    - TRAI (Box 153)
    - TRAU (Box 153)
    - TRE (Box 153)
    - TRI (Box 153)
    - TRO (Box 153)
    - TS (Box 153)
    - TUC (Box 154)
    - TUCKER, STERLING, THE HON. (Box 154)
    - TUD (Box 154)
    - TUM (Box 154)
    - TURNER (Box 154)
    - TURP (Box 154)
    - TY (Box 154)
  - Personal or Organizational - U, V
    - U (Box 154)
    - UN (Box 154)
    - UNITED (Box 154)
    - UNITED S (Box 154)
    - UNIVERSITY (Box 154)
    - UNIVERSITY, M (Box 154)
    - UNJ (Box 154)
    - UR (Box 154)
    - US (Box 154)
    - V (Box 155)
    - VAL (Box 155)
    - VAN (Box 155)
    - VAND (Box 155)
    - VANE (Box 155)
    - VANN (Box 155)
    - VAN WAGENEN, CHARLES R. (Box 155)
    - VAR (Box 155)
    - VAU (Box 155)
    - VE (Box 155)
    - VEN (Box 155)
    - VER (Box 155)
    - VET (Box 155)
    - VI (Box 156)
    - VIN (Box 156)
    - VIS (Box 156)
    - VO (Box 156)
    - VON (Box 156)
    - VOT (Box 156)
  - Personal or Organizational - W
    - W (Box 156)
    - WAGNER (Box 156)
    - WAH (Box 156)
    - WALKER (Box 156)
    - WALL (Box 156)
    - WALS (Box 156)
    - WALT (Box 156)
    - WAM (Box 156)
    - WAR (Box 157)
    - WARNER (Box 157)
    - WARNI (Box 157)
    - WARS (Box 157)
    - WASHINGTON (Box 157)
    - WAT (Box 157)
    - WATS (Box 157)
    - WE (Box 157)
    - WEB (Box 157)
    - WEC (Box 157)
    - WEI (Box 158)
    - WEIN (Box 158)
    - WEIR (Box 158)
    - WEISS (Box 158)
    - WEIT (Box 158)
    - WELL (Box 158)
    - WEM (Box 158)
    - WER (Box 158)
    - WEST (Box 158)
    - WESTM (Box 158)
    - WH (Box 158)
    - WHEE (Box 158)
    - WHI (Box 158)
    - WHITE (Box 158)
    - WHITE, M (Box 158)
    - WHITEA (Box 159)
    - WI (Box 159)
    - WIL (Box 159)
    - WILL (Box 159)
    - WILLIAMS (Box 159)
    - WILLIAMS, E (Box 159)
    - WILLIAMS, K (Box 159)
    - WILLIAMS, T (Box 159)
    - WILLIAMSON (Box 159)
    - WILLIS (Box 159)
    - WILSON (Box 160)
    - WILSON, E (Box 160)
    - WILSON, M (Box 160)
    - WILT (Box 160)
    - WINT (Box 160)
    - WIS (Box 160)
    - WO (Box 160)
    - WOLF (Box 160)
    - WOLFE (Box 160)
    - WOM (Box 160)
    - WOOD (Box 160)
    - WOODS (Box 160)
    - WOR (Box 160)
    - WR (Box 161)
    - WS (Box 161)
    - WY (Box 161)
  - Personal or Organizational - X, Y
    - X (Box 161)
    - Y (Box 161)
    - YE (Box 161)
    - YO (Box 161)
    - YOUNG (Box 161)
    - YOUNG, L (Box 161)
    - YOUNGA (Box 161)
  - Personal or Organizational - Z
    - Z (Box 162)
    - ZARB, FRANK G., THE HON. (Box 162)
    - ZAS (Box 162)
    - ZI (Box 162)
    - ZO (Box 162)
- Subject File, 2
  - Agriculture (AG), 1
    - AG - AGRICULTURE (Box 163)
    - AG 3-1 - Protection Programs in Marketing (Box 163)
    - AG 4 - Price Support (Box 163)
    - AG 6 - Rural Development (Box 163)
  - Art (AR), 2
    - AR - ART, 1975 (Box 163)
    - AR - ART, 1976 (Box 163)
    - AR 2 - Museums (Box 163)
    - AR 3 - Music (Box 163)
    - AR 3-1 - Service Bands & Service Choirs (Box 163)
    - AR 4 - Painting - Drawing (Box 163)
    - AR 6 - Sculpture (Box 163)
    - AR 7 - Theatre (Box 163)
  - Atomic Energy (AT), 3
    - AT - ATOMIC ENERGY (Box 163)
  - Business Economics (BE), 4
    - BE - BUSINESS - ECONOMICS (Box 163)
    - BE 2 - Domestic Trade (Box 163)
    - BE 2-2 - Monopoly-Antimonopoly (Box 163)
    - BE 3 - Economic Controls (Box 163)
    - BE 4 - Industry (Box 163)
    - BE 4-3 - Minority Business (Box 163)
    - BE 4-4 - Small Business (Box 163)
    - BE 5 - National Economy (Box 163)
    - BE 5 - National Economy, 1975 May 1 (Box 163)
    - BE 5 - National Economy, 1975 July 1-15 (Box 163)
    - BE 5 - National Economy, 1976 January 16-February 20 (Box 163)
    - BE 5-1 - Business Trends (Box 163)
    - BE 5-2 - Cost of Living (Box 163)
    - BE 5-3 - Inflation - Money Scarcity (Box 163)
    - BE 5-4 - National Income - Product data (Box 163)
    - BE 5-5 - Recessions - Depressions (Box 163)
    - BE 5-6 - Domestic Problems (Box 163)
    - BE 5-6 - Domestic Problems, 1976 (Box 163)
    - BE 6 - Patents-Inventions-Copyrights-Trademarks (Box 163)
  - Civil Aviation (CA), 5
    - CA - CIVIL AVIATION (Box 164)
    - CA 2 - Airports (Box 164)
    - CA 4 - Routes - Navigation (Box 164)
  - Commodities (CM), 6
    - CM/A-Z - COMMODITIES (Box 164)
  - Countries (CO), 7
    - CO - COUNTRIES (Box 164)
    - CO/A (Box 164)
    - CO/B (Box 164)
    - CO/C (Box 164)
    - CO/China (Box 164)
    - CO/D (Box 164)
    - CO/E (Box 164)
    - CO/F (Box 164)
    - CO/G (Box 164)
    - CO/H (Box 164)
    - CO/I (Box 164)
    - CO/J (Box 164)
    - CO/K (Box 164)
    - CO/L (Box 164)
    - CO/M (Box 164)
    - CO/N (Box 164)
    - CO/O (Box 164)
    - CO/P (Box 164)
    - CO/Q (Box 164)
    - CO/R (Box 164)
    - CO/S (Box 164)
    - CO/T (Box 164)
    - CO/U (Box 164)
    - CO/V (Box 164)
    - CO/W (Box 164)
    - CO/XYZ (Box 164)
  - Disasters (DI), 8
    - DI - DISASTERS (Box 165)
    - DI - Earthquakes (Box 165)
  - Education (ED), 9
    - ED - EDUCATION (Box 165)
    - ED 1 - Buildings-Grounds-Facilities (Box 165)
    - ED 2 - Invitations for Campuses (Box 165)
    - ED 3 - Libraries (Box 165)
    - ED 4 - Scholarships-Fellowships-Grants (Box 165)
    - ED 5-1 - Busing (Box 165)
    - ED 6 - Teachers (Box 165)
    - ED 6-1 - University and College Professors (Box 165)
    - ED 7 - Teaching Methods (visual aids-TV) (Box 165)
  - Employment Assistance (EM), 10
    - EM - Employment Assistance (Box 165)
  - Endorsements (EN), 11
    - EN - ENDORSEMENTS (Box 165)
    - EN 10 - Supreme Court Judges (Box 165)
    - EN 11 - United States Circuit Court Judges (Box 165)
    - EN 12 - United States Attorneys (Box 165)
    - EN 13 - United States Marshals (Box 165)
  - Federal Aid (FA), 12
    - FA - FEDERAL AID (Box 165)
    - FA - FEDERAL AID, 1975 August 1 (Box 165)
    - FA 2 - Arts (Box 165)
    - FA 3 - Education (Box 165)
    - FA 4 - Highways (Box 165)
    - FA 5 - Housing (Box 165)
    - FA 6 - Public Health (Box 165)
  - Federal Government (FE), 13
    - FE - FEDERAL GOVERNMENT (Box 165)
    - FE 1 - Bill of Rights (Box 165)
    - FE 2 - Capitol (Box 165)
    - FE 3-1/Chiang Kai-Shek - Deaths-Funerals (Box 165)
    - FE 3-1/Franco Francisco (Box 165)
    - FE 6 - Executive Orders (Box 165)
    - FE 7 - Heraldry (Box 165)
    - FE 7-1 - Flags (Box 165)
    - FE 7-1-3 - Vice President's Flag (Box 165)
    - FE 7-2-2 - Vice President's Seals - Coat of Arms (Box 165)
    - FE 8 - History-Historical Events (Bicentenial) (Box 165)
    - FE 8, 1975 June 1 (Box 165)
    - FE 8, 1976 January 1 (Box 165)
    - FE 8, 1976 March 1 (Box 165)
    - FE 9 - Management Improvement Program (Box 165)
    - FE 12-1 - Vice President's Lib raries (Box 165)
    - FE 14 - Records-Archives (Box 165)
    - FE 14-1 - Access to Records (Box 165)
    - FE 15 - Certificates and Documents (Box 165)
  - Federal Government Organizations (FG), 14
    - FG - FEDERAL GOVERNMENT ORGANIZATIONS (Box 165)
    - FG/Agencies - A (Box 165)
    - FG/Agencies - B (Box 165)
    - FG/Agencies - C (Box 165)
    - FG/Agencies - CIA (Box 165)
    - FG/Agencies - CIA, 1975 April (Box 165)
    - FG/Agencies - D (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - E (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - F (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - G (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - H (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - I (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - J,K,L,M,N (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - O (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - P (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - Q,R,S,T,U (Box 166)
    - FG/Agencies - V,W,X,Y,Z (Box 166)
    - FG/Water Quality (Box 166)
    - FG/Water Quality, 1976 (Box 166)
    - FG 1 - President of the U.S. - His Administration (Box 166)
    - FG 1-1 - Delegations of Authority (Box 166)
    - FG 1-2 - Personal Representatives (Box 166)
    - FG 1-3 - Inaugurations (Box 166)
    - FG 1-4 - Proposed Agency or Commission (Box 166)
    - FG 2 - Former Presidents (Box 166)
    - FG 2-1 - Washington, George (Box 166)
    - FG 2-2 - Adams, John (Box 166)
    - FG 2-3 - Jefferson, Thomas (Box 166)
    - FG 2-6 - Adams, John Quincy (Box 166)
    - FG 2-16 - Lincoln, Abraham (Box 166)
    - FG 2-24 - McKinley, William (Box 166)
    - FG 2-25 - Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 166)
    - FG 2-29 - Coolidge, Calvin (Box 166)
    - FG 2-31 - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Box 166)
    - FG 2-32 - Truman, Harry S. (Box 166)
    - FG 2-33 - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 166)
    - FG 2-34 - Kennedy, John F. (Box 166)
    - FG 2-35 - Johnson, Lyndon (Box 166)
    - FG 2-36 - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 166)
    - FG 3 - Transition to Incoming Administration (Box 166)
    - FG 4 - Agencies, Boards, Commissions/A-Z (Box 166)
    - FG 4-1 - Agencies, Boards, Commissions (Proposed) (Box 166)
    - FG 4-1 - Agencies, Boards, Commissions (Proposed)/A-Z (Box 166)
    - FG 5 - Executive Branch (Box 166)
    - FG 5-1 - White House Administration (Box 166)
    - FG 6 - Judicial Branch (Courts) (Box 166)
    - FG 7 - Legislative Branch (Congress) (Box 166)
    - FG 8 - Cabinet (Box 166)
  - Finance (FI), 15
    - FI - FINANCE (Box 167)
    - FI 1 - Accounting (Box 167)
    - FI 1-2 - Disbursements-Expenditures (Box 167)
    - FI 2 - Banks - Banking (Box 167)
    - FI 3 - Bonds - Stocks - Investments (Box 167)
    - FI 4 - Budget - Appropriations (Box 167)
    - FI 4 - Budget Agencies/A-Z (Box 167)
    - FI 4-1 - Allocations (budget) (Box 167)
    - FI 4-3 - Estimates (budgets) (Box 167)
    - FI 5 - Credit Loans (Box 167)
    - FI 5-4 - Housing Loans (Box 167)
    - FI 5-6 - Schools-Institutions (loans) (Box 167)
    - FI 5-6-1 - Student-Teacher loans (Box 167)
    - FI 5-7 - Small business loans (Box 167)
    - FI 6 - Credit Unions (Box 167)
    - FI 9 - Monetary Systems (Box 167)
    - FI 10 - Public Debt (Box 167)
    - FI 11 - Taxation (Box 167)
    - FI 11-1 - Estate - Gift (taxation) (Box 167)
    - FI 11-3 - Excise Tax (Box 167)
    - FI 11-4 - Income Tax (Box 167)
  - Foreign Affairs (FO), 16
    - FO - FOREIGN AFFAIRS (Box 167)
    - FO 2 - Diplomatic - Consular Relations (Box 167)
    - FO 2 - U.S. Ambassadors/Countries A-Z (Box 167)
    - FO 2-1 - Personal or Special Rank of Ambassador (Box 167)
    - FO 3 - Economic-Technical Development (Box 167)
    - FO 3-2 - Mutual Security (Box 167)
    - FO 3-2 - Mutual Security/ countries A-Z (Box 167)
    - FO 4 - Financial Relations (Box 167)
    - FO 4-1 - Balance of Payments (Box 167)
    - FO 4-3 - Loans - Funds (Box 167)
    - FO 5 - Information-Exchange Activities (Box 167)
    - FO 5-1 - Educational Exchange Activities (Box 167)
    - FO 5-2 - Scientific-Cultural-Business (Box 167)
    - FO 5-3 - Foreign Publications (Box 167)
    - FO 7 - International Law (Box 167)
    - FO 8 - International Travel (Box 167)
    - FO 8-1 - Letters of Introduction (Box 167)
    - FO 8-2 - Passports - Visas (Box 167)
    - FO 9 - Treaties (Box 167)
  - Gifts (GI), 17
    - GI - GIFTS (received by the Vice President) (Box 167)
    - GI 1 - Gifts from the Vice President (Box 167)
    - GI 1 - Gifts by name/A-Z (Box 167)
    - GI 2 - Gifts to the Vice President or his family (Box 167)
    - GI 2 - Gifts by name/A-Z (Box 167)
    - GI 2-1 - Clothing-Wearing Apparel (Box 167)
    - GI 2-1 - Clothing by Donor/A-Z (Box 167)
    - GI 2-2 - Flowers - Shrubs (Box 167)
    - GI 2-2 - Flowers - Shrubs/A-Z (Box 167)
    - GI 2-3 - Food - Drinks (Box 167)
    - GI 2-3 - Food - Drinks/A-Z (Box 167)
    - GI 2-4 - Historical Documents/A-Z (Box 168)
    - GI 2-5 - Hobbies - Sports (Box 168)
    - GI 2-5 - Hobbies - Sports/A-Z (Box 168)
    - GI 2-6 Household Items/A-Z (Box 168)
    - GI 2-7 - Jewelry - Cosmetics/A-Z (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/A (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/B (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/C (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/D (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/E (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/F (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/G (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/H (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/I (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/J (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/K (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/L (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/M (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/N (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/O (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/P (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/Q-R (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/S (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/T (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/U-V (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/W (Box 168)
    - GI 2-8 - Literature-Books-Poetry/X,Y,Z (Box 168)
    - GI 2-9 - Music Recordings/A-Z (Box 169)
    - GI 2-10 - Office equipment/A-Z (Box 169)
    - GI 2-11 - Pets - Livestock/A-Z (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/A (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/B (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/C (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/D (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/E (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/F (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/G (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/H (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/I-J (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/K (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/L (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/M (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/N (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/O (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/P (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/Q-R (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/S (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/T (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/U-V (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/W (Box 169)
    - GI 2-12 - Pictures-Photographs-Portraits-Art Work/X,Y,Z (Box 169)
    - GI 2-13 - Religious Articles/A-M (Box 169)
    - GI 2-13 - Religious Articles/N-Z (Box 169)
    - GI 2-14 - Smoking/A-Z (Box 169)
    - GI 2-15 - Souvenirs (Box 169)
    - GI 2-15 - Souvenirs/A-L (Box 169)
    - GI 2-15 - Souvenirs/M-Z (Box 169)
    - GiI 2-16 - Toys - Children's Gifts/A-Z (Box 169)
    - GI 2-17 - Money/A-Z (Box 169)
    - GI 3 - Gifts from or to the United States (Box 169)
    - GI 3 - Gifts from or to the United States by country/A-Z (Box 169)
  - Health (HE), 18
    - HE - HEALTH (Box 169)
    - HE 1 - Diseases (Box 169)
    - HE 1-1 - Alcoholism (Box 169)
    - HE 1-2 - blindness - includes dyslexia (Box 169)
    - HE 1-3 - Cancer (Box 169)
    - HE 1-4 - Heart (Box 169)
    - HE 1-5 Mental Disorders (Box 169)
    - HE 2 - Doctors-Dentists-Nurses (Box 170)
    - HE 3 - Food-Nutrition (Box 170)
    - HE 4 - Health Services (Box 170)
    - HE 4-1 - Chronic Diseases-Health of Aged (Box 170)
    - HE 4-2 - Environmental-Occupational Health (Box 170)
    - HE 5 - Hospitals-Medical Care (Box 170)
    - HE 6 - Medicines-Drugs-Serums (Box 170)
    - HE 6-1 - Narcotics (Box 170)
    - HE 7 - Pollution (Box 170)
    - HE 7-1 - Air pollution (Box 170)
    - HE 7-2 - Environment-Pollution (Box 170)
    - HE 7-4 - Water Pollution (Box 170)
    - HE 7-4 - Water Pollution, 1975 December 1 (Box 170)
    - HE 8-2 - Sewerage Systems (Box 170)
  - Highway - Bridges (HI), 19
    - HI - HIGHWAYS-BRIDGES (Box 170)
    - HI 1 - Bridges-Overpasses-Tunnels (Box 170)
    - HI 3 - Plans-Specifications for Highways (Box 170)
  - Holidays (HO), 20
    - HO - HOLIDAYS (Box 170)
    - HO - HOLIDAYS by name/A-Z (Box 170)
  - Housing (HS), 21
    - HS - HOUSING (Box 170)
    - HS 2 - Public Housing Programs (Box 170)
    - HS 3 - Urban Renewal-Slum Clearance (Box 170)
  - Human Rights (HU), 22
    - HU - HUMAN RIGHTS (Box 170)
    - HU 1 - Citizenship (Box 170)
    - HU 2 - Equality (Box 170)
    - HU 2-1 - Education-Schooling (Box 170)
    - HU 2-2 - Employment (Box 170)
    - HU 2-3 - Housing (Box 170)
    - HU 2-4 - Voting (Box 170)
    - HU 2-5 - Women (Box 170)
    - HU 3 - Freedoms (Box 170)
    - HU 3-1 - Divil Disturbances-Riots (Box 170)
    - HU 3-1 - Divil Disturbances-Riots by state/A-Z (Box 170)
    - HU 3-2 - Press (Box 170)
    - HU 4 - Genocide (Box 170)
    - HU 5 - Ideologies (Box 170)
    - HU 6 - Harrassment (Box 171)
  - Immigration (IM), 23
    - IM - IMMIGRATION-NATURALIZATION (Box 171)
    - IM - IMMIGRATION-NATURALIZATION by individual/A-Z (Box 171)
  - Indian Affairs (IN), 24
    - IN - INDIAN AFFAIRS (Box 171)
    - IN - INDIAN AFFAIRS by tribe/A-Z (Box 171)
  - Insurance (IS), 25
    - IS - INSURANCE (Box 171)
    - IS 1 - Accident-Hospital-Medical-Health (Box 171)
    - IS 2 - Crop-Farm-tenant (Box 171)
    - IS 3 - Disaster (Box 171)
    - IS 5 - Life (Box 171)
  - International Organizations (IT), 26
    - IT - INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATIONS (Box 171)
    - IT - INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATIONS by name/A-Z (Box 171)
    - IT 1 - United Nations (Box 171)
  - Judicial - Legal Matters (JL), 27
    - JL - JUDICIAL-LEGAL MATTERS (Box 171)
    - JL 1 - Amnesties-Clemency-Pardons (Box 171)
    - JL 2 - Civil Matters (Box 171)
    - JL 2-1 - Anti-Trust Cases (Box 171)
    - JL 3 - Criminal Matters (Box 171)
    - JL 3-1 - Assassination or attempt (Box 171)
    - JL 3-1 - Assassination or attempt by individual/A-Z (Box 171)
    - JL 4-3 - Judicial decisions (courts) (Box 171)
    - JL 5 - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 171)
    - JL 6 - Law Enforcement-Police Matters (Box 171)
    - JL 7 - Lawyers-Legal Aid (Box 171)
  - Labor-Management Relations (LA), 28
    - LA - LABOR-MANAGEMENT RELATIONS (Box 171)
    - LA 2 - conditions-Employment-Unemployment (Box 171)
    - LA 4 - Investigations (Labor) (Box 171)
    - LA 5 - Migratory Labor-Seasonal Labor (Box 171)
    - LA 6 - Strikes-Work Stoppages-Arbitration (Box 171)
    - LA 6-8 - Construction workers strikes (Box 171)
    - LA 6-16 - Maritime strikes (Box 171)
    - LA 6-29 - Steel-Iron Workers strikes (Box 171)
    - LA 7 - Unions (Box 171)
    - LA 8 - Wage-Hours (Box 171)
    - LA 9 - Welfare-Pensions-Retirement (Box 171)
  - Legislation (LE), 29
    - LE - LEGISLATION (Box 171)
    - LE - LEGISLATION, 1976 (Box 171)
    - LE 1 - Filibustering (Box 171)
    - LE 2 - Lobbying (Box 171)
    - LE 4 - Vetoes and Repeals (Box 171)
    - LE 5 - Voting Records of Members of Congress (Box 171)
    - LE 6 Congressional Hearings (Box 171)
    - LE 6-1 - Confirmation hearings for Vice President (Box 171)
  - Cities (LG), 30
    - LG - CITIES (Box 171)
    - LG - CITIES by city/A-K (Box 171)
    - LG - CITIES by city/L-Z (Box 171)
    - LG - New York City (Box 171)
    - LG - New York City, 1975 December 1 (Box 171)
    - LG - New York City, 1976 December 16 (Box 171)
  - Medals - Awards (MA), 31
    - MA - MEDALS-AWARDS (Box 171)
    - MA 1 - Civil Service (Box 171)
    - MA 2 - Civilian Service (Box 171)
    - MA 4 - Presidential Commemorative Medals (Box 171)
    - MA 5-1 - Congressional Medal of Honor (Box 171)
    - MA 5-6 - Purple Heart (Box 171)
  - Meetings - Conferences (MC), 32
    - MC - MEETINGS-CONFERENCES (Box 172)
    - MC - MEETINGS-CONFERENCES, 1975 August 1 (Box 172)
    - MC 1 - Domestic Forums (Box 172)
    - MC 1 - Domestic Forums/Austin (Box 172)
    - MC 1 - Domestic Forums/Denver (Box 172)
    - MC 1 - Domestic Forums/Indianapolis (Box 172)